<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Silver Wolf Web Solutions</string>
    <string name="sobre_a_empresa">Sobre a Empresa</string>
    <string name="desc_empresa">Bacon ipsum dolor amet chicken meatloaf spare ribs leberkas tongue boudin flank venison meatball corned beef drumstick pancetta short loin filet mignon. Meatloaf bresaola picanha pork belly strip steak. Drumstick boudin bresaola porchetta shoulder hamburger ground round swine ham meatball ball tip. Pork ball tip frankfurter burgdoggen, t-bone sausage turkey jowl doner sirloin. Doner shankle burgdoggen turkey hamburger. Ground round tail kielbasa tenderloin ribeye leberkas buffalo biltong shankle bresaola jerky cow turkey pig pancetta. Pork chop shoulder swine hamburger. Tongue jerky meatball, bresaola kevin doner kielbasa venison ham hock. Spare ribs pastrami shoulder bresaola corned beef strip steak. Andouille ball tip porchetta turducken, cupim venison fatback jowl short loin flank swine spare ribs sausage t-bone doner. Swine tongue prosciutto shoulder doner fatback andouille pork boudin bresaola kielbasa meatloaf leberkas. Rump landjaeger tongue pastrami alcatra spare ribs pork andouille ground round fatback doner t-bone salami brisket. Picanha spare ribs ground round strip steak ribeye chuck. Buffalo frankfurter chicken pork flank, drumstick jowl ham ball tip doner. Tail bresaola pork loin leberkas jerky, kielbasa landjaeger shoulder ball tip filet mignon shankle strip steak pork belly ground round. Turducken t-bone ribeye, fatback pork loin bresaola doner porchetta. Rump andouille filet mignon, beef shankle shank sausage corned beef cupim. Ham meatball prosciutto filet mignon, shoulder spare ribs ribeye beef ribs ham hock jowl pork loin kevin chuck ball tip.</string>
    <string name="servicos">Serviços</string>
    <string name="email_contato_silverwolf">E-mail: Contato@silverwolf.com.br</string>
    <string name="telefone">Telefone: (11) 3333-3333</string>
    <string name="celular">Celular: (11) 99999-9999</string>
</resources>
